# Addison Moore

**LinkedIn**: <u>linkedin.com/in/addison-moore</u>

**Github**: github.com/addisong12 **Website**: addisonmoore.me

I'm a full stack software engineer, data wizard, and linux evangelist from the San Francisco Bay Area. I'm a seasoned developer with over 8 years experience working in tech. Over the past few years I've worked as a full stack engineer on small teams where I've gained experience with a variety of tools and languages to bring applications from concept to

## **SKILLS**

Languages: Javascript/Typescript, Python, HTML, CSS, Bash, French Frameworks and Libraries: React, Next.js, Flask, Django, React-Native Backend: Node.js, Express, Python, Linux, Docker, NGINX, Restful APIs, Micro

Data: MongoDB, PostgreSQL, Snowflake, GCP, GraphQL, Tableau, Power BI, Airflow, DBT, Pandas, Jupyter

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# Stratus Data / Software Engineer, Data Engineer

September 2021 - APRIL 2023, REMOTE

- As the sole full stack engineer at stratus data, I built and launched our client facing portal. I also worked on several internal tools to improve the efficacy of our team and enable data scientists on the team to launch client facing dashboards.
- As a data engineer, I worked with clients to build data pipelines using a variety of tools, including Airflow, DBT, Snowflake, BigQuery, SQL, Python and more. I also created APIs to transform and analyze data using natural language processing and market basket analysis.

# Tide Pool Tech / Full Stack Software Engineer

MAY 2020 - Present, SAN FRANCISCO

- Built a full stack cryptocurrency trading platform to take advantage of arbitrage opportunities between US and South Korean markets.
- Built bespoke websites for clients with custom content management systems, primarily using the MERN stack (Mongo, Express, Node, and React).

## **Quantum Metric /** Software Engineer, Customer Success Team

JULY 2019 - JULY 2020, SAN FRANCISCO

- Primary engineer servicing over \$5M in contracts for brands such as Western Union, eBay and Lululemon.
- Wrote clean and readable Javascript to gather analytics data and help brands measure their KPIs.
- · Worked with top brands to implement Quantum Metric on their digital platforms.

## **The Bosco /** Product Designer

JUNE 2015 - SEPTEMBER 2018, SAN FRANCISCO

- Lead designer on new core products including the Bosco Lite and Multicam. These products generated over \$10M in revenue during my time at The Bosco.
- Launched the Bosco's San Francisco office. Hired and managed the SF team which consisted of at least 6 operations assistants and event staff throughout my tenure.

## County of Mendocino / Program Specialist

OCTOBER 2012 - JUNE 2015, UKIAH, CA

### **EDUCATION**

#### California State University of Monterey Bay

AUGUST 2007 - MAY 2012, SEASIDE, CA Computer Science, B.S.